// import shuffleArray from "../helpers/shuffleArray.js";

// import { getRandomItem } from "../helpers/shuffleAnswer.js";
// const getRandomItem = (array) =>
//   array[Math.floor(Math.random() * array.length)];

export const JimCarreyQuestions = [
  {
    question: "In which movie does Jim Carrey play a pet detective?",
    options: [
      "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective",
      "The Mask",
      "Dumb and Dumber",
      "Liar Liar",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Jim Carrey’s character in *The Mask*?",
    options: ["Bruce Nolan", "Stanley Ipkiss", "Fletcher Reede", "Ace Ventura"],
    correctAnswer: "Stanley Ipkiss",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Jim Carrey movie features him as a lawyer who can't lie for 24 hours?",
    options: ["Yes Man", "Liar Liar", "The Cable Guy", "Bruce Almighty"],
    correctAnswer: "Liar Liar",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Jim Carrey play a character who lives his entire life on a TV show?",
    options: [
      "Man on the Moon",
      "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind",
      "The Truman Show",
      "Me, Myself & Irene",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Truman Show",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Dumb and Dumber*, what is the name of Jim Carrey's character?",
    options: [
      "Lloyd Christmas",
      "Harry Dunne",
      "Stanley Ipkiss",
      "Bruce Nolan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Lloyd Christmas",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Jim Carrey as a man who can suddenly do anything he wishes after receiving God's powers?",
    options: ["Yes Man", "Liar Liar", "The Mask", "Bruce Almighty"],
    correctAnswer: "Bruce Almighty",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind*, what is the name of Jim Carrey's character?",
    options: [
      "Andy Kaufman",
      "Joel Barish",
      "Lloyd Christmas",
      "Walter Sparrow",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Joel Barish",
  },
  {
    question: "Which film features Jim Carrey as the villain, The Riddler?",
    options: [
      "The Mask",
      "Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events",
      "Kick-Ass 2",
      "Batman Forever",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Batman Forever",
  },
  {
    question: "In *How the Grinch Stole Christmas*, who does Jim Carrey play?",
    options: [
      "The Mayor of Whoville",
      "The Grinch",
      "Cindy Lou Who",
      "Max the Dog",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Grinch",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a man who says 'yes' to everything for an entire year?",
    options: ["Yes Man", "Liar Liar", "Bruce Almighty", "The Cable Guy"],
    correctAnswer: "Yes Man",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Jim Carrey star as a man with split personalities?",
    options: [
      "The Mask",
      "Me, Myself & Irene",
      "The Number 23",
      "Ace Ventura: When Nature Calls",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Me, Myself & Irene",
  },
  {
    question: "In *The Cable Guy*, what is Jim Carrey’s character's job?",
    options: ["Lawyer", "Detective", "Cable installer", "Teacher"],
    correctAnswer: "Cable installer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a con artist who falls in love with his fellow inmate?",
    options: [
      "Man on the Moon",
      "Liar Liar",
      "I Love You Phillip Morris",
      "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I Love You Phillip Morris",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Man on the Moon*, Jim Carrey plays which real-life comedian?",
    options: [
      "Andy Kaufman",
      "George Carlin",
      "Robin Williams",
      "Richard Pryor",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Andy Kaufman",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Jim Carrey movie is centered around the number 23?",
    options: [
      "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind",
      "The Number 23",
      "The Truman Show",
      "Me, Myself & Irene",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Number 23",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events*, which character does Jim Carrey portray?",
    options: [
      "Violet Baudelaire",
      "Klaus Baudelaire",
      "Uncle Monty",
      "Count Olaf",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Count Olaf",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Majestic*, Jim Carrey's character suffers from which condition?",
    options: ["Paranoia", "Schizophrenia", "Narcolepsy", "Amnesia"],
    correctAnswer: "Amnesia",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a detective who speaks with animals?",
    options: [
      "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective",
      "Liar Liar",
      "Bruce Almighty",
      "Yes Man",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Dumb and Dumber To*, how many years later do Jim Carrey and Jeff Daniels return to their roles?",
    options: ["15 years", "20 years", "10 years", "25 years"],
    correctAnswer: "20 years",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Jim Carrey film features him as a character named Carl Allen, who is forced to say yes to everything?",
    options: ["Liar Liar", "Yes Man", "The Truman Show", "Me, Myself & Irene"],
    correctAnswer: "Yes Man",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a man trapped in a fake reality created for television?",
    options: [
      "Man on the Moon",
      "The Truman Show",
      "Bruce Almighty",
      "The Number 23",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Truman Show",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Liar Liar*, what event causes Jim Carrey's character to tell the truth for 24 hours?",
    options: [
      "An accident",
      "His son's birthday wish",
      "A curse",
      "A court order",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "His son's birthday wish",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a man with obsessive tendencies related to the number 23?",
    options: [
      "The Number 23",
      "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind",
      "Me, Myself & Irene",
      "The Majestic",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Number 23",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Bruce Almighty*, who plays God alongside Jim Carrey?",
    options: [
      "Samuel L. Jackson",
      "Morgan Freeman",
      "Denzel Washington",
      "Laurence Fishburne",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Morgan Freeman",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which film does Jim Carrey play a man who becomes a superhero after wearing a magical mask?",
    options: ["Liar Liar", "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective", "Yes Man", "The Mask"],
    correctAnswer: "The Mask",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Jim Carrey as an unlucky TV news reporter who gains divine powers?",
    options: [
      "Liar Liar",
      "Bruce Almighty",
      "The Truman Show",
      "The Cable Guy",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Bruce Almighty",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Me, Myself & Irene*, what is Jim Carrey's profession?",
    options: ["Lawyer", "Veterinarian", "Police officer", "Cable installer"],
    correctAnswer: "Police officer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a detective who helps find a missing dolphin mascot?",
    options: [
      "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective",
      "The Mask",
      "Yes Man",
      "The Truman Show",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ace Ventura: Pet Detective",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a paranoid cable installer who becomes obsessed with his client?",
    options: ["Liar Liar", "The Cable Guy", "Yes Man", "The Truman Show"],
    correctAnswer: "The Cable Guy",
  },
  {
    question: "In which movie does Jim Carrey play Ebenezer Scrooge?",
    options: ["A Christmas Carol", "The Grinch", "The Mask", "The Majestic"],
    correctAnswer: "A Christmas Carol",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a character who is desperately trying to erase the memory of his ex-girlfriend?",
    options: [
      "The Truman Show",
      "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind",
      "Me, Myself & Irene",
      "Bruce Almighty",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie stars Jim Carrey as a desperate man who steals the identity of a famous bank robber?",
    options: [
      "I Love You Phillip Morris",
      "Dumb and Dumber",
      "Fun with Dick and Jane",
      "The Truman Show",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Fun with Dick and Jane",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Dumb and Dumber*, what item do Jim Carrey and Jeff Daniels travel across the country to return?",
    options: ["A wallet", "A briefcase", "A dog", "A hat"],
    correctAnswer: "A briefcase",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events*, what is the primary goal of Jim Carrey's character, Count Olaf?",
    options: [
      "Stealing the Baudelaire fortune",
      "Saving the children",
      "Becoming famous",
      "Escaping jail",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stealing the Baudelaire fortune",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Jim Carrey play a character named Walter Sparrow obsessed with a mysterious book?",
    options: [
      "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind",
      "The Number 23",
      "Yes Man",
      "The Truman Show",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Number 23",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which animated movie features Jim Carrey as the voice of Horton the elephant?",
    options: ["Horton Hears a Who!", "The Lorax", "Ice Age", "Despicable Me"],
    correctAnswer: "Horton Hears a Who!",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which film does Jim Carrey play a man living in a controlled, 24/7 televised world?",
    options: ["The Truman Show", "Liar Liar", "Bruce Almighty", "Yes Man"],
    correctAnswer: "The Truman Show",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Jim Carrey movie is set in a fictional town called Seahaven?",
    options: ["Dumb and Dumber", "The Truman Show", "The Mask", "Liar Liar"],
    correctAnswer: "The Truman Show",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a man with three adopted sons who thinks he's found his biological father?",
    options: ["The Number 23", "Liar Liar", "Yes Man", "Me, Myself & Irene"],
    correctAnswer: "Me, Myself & Irene",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which movie does Jim Carrey play a character named Charlie who has a split personality?",
    options: [
      "Me, Myself & Irene",
      "The Mask",
      "The Cable Guy",
      "The Truman Show",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Me, Myself & Irene",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which animated film features Jim Carrey as the voice of an evil villain named Dr. Robotnik?",
    options: [
      "The Lorax",
      "Sonic the Hedgehog",
      "Horton Hears a Who!",
      "Despicable Me",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Sonic the Hedgehog",
  },
  {
    question: "In *A Christmas Carol*, which character does Jim Carrey voice?",
    options: [
      "Ebenezer Scrooge",
      "The Ghost of Christmas Past",
      "The Grinch",
      "Jacob Marley",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ebenezer Scrooge",
  },
  {
    question: "In *Bruce Almighty*, what does Jim Carrey's character wish for?",
    options: [
      "To get a promotion",
      "To win the lottery",
      "To become God",
      "To travel the world",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To become God",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In *The Mask*, what magical object transforms Jim Carrey's character?",
    options: ["A ring", "A necklace", "A mask", "A hat"],
    correctAnswer: "A mask",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which movie features Jim Carrey as a man who can no longer tell a lie after his son's wish?",
    options: ["Liar Liar", "Yes Man", "Bruce Almighty", "The Cable Guy"],
    correctAnswer: "Liar Liar",
  },
];

export default JimCarreyQuestions;
